你真是爛透了， 湯姆
You're a jerk, Thom.
聽著希莉亞， 我們必須順著我們的感覺走
Look Celia, we have to follow our passions;
... 你熱愛機械工學， 而我只是想去太空中耍帥一下
...you have your robotics, and I just want to be awesome in space.
你為什麼不肯承認你被我的機械手臂嚇壞了？
Why don't you just admit that you're freaked out by my robot hand?
我沒有害怕， 只是...
I'm not freaked out by- it's...
... 好好好！
...alright! Fine!
我承認 我被嚇傻了！ 我還做惡夢被它追著跑...
I'm freaked out! I have nightmares that I'm being chased...
... 被這些巨大的奪命機器爪子追殺...
...by these giant robotic claws of death...
隨便你怎麼說。 湯姆， 我們之間玩完了
"Fourty years later" Whatever, Thom. We're done.
機器人記憶同步鎖定完成！
Robot's memory synced and locked!
這個挺詭異的
This is pretty freaky.
你是不是該下去了吧？
Shouldn't you be down there?
我昨天聽到你們這些傢伙的談話
I heard you guys talking last night.
你知道的， 這不是我的錯
It's not my fault, you know.
準備好了嗎？
Are you ready?
你當然準備好了， 你是個搖滾明星嘛
Of course you're ready, you're a rockstar.
情況如何， 貝里？
How's it looking, Barley?
我們應該有10分鐘左右的時間...
We should have about ten minutes...
好的， 棒極了
Well that's perfect.
一分鐘後開始！ 全部的系統啟動！ 對， 你也是， 快點！
We're on in one! All systems go! Yeah you, go!
快！ 動起來！ 快快快！
Go! Move your asses! Go go go!
這個我喜歡！ 拜託， 快！
I love it! Come on, go!
很好
That's nice.
沒什麼好擔心的
Nothing to worry about.
湯姆
Thom.
她在那
There she is.
就是現在
Now.
你是愛她的
You love her.
她就是你的熱情
She is your passion!
溫柔點
Be tender to her.
要誠懇！ 溫柔些
Be honest! Eh- be tender.
讓她回憶起什麼是愛
Remind her what love is.
... 好， 開演！
...and, action!
記憶覆寫開始！
Memory overwrite in progress!
你真是爛透了， 湯姆！
You're a jerk, Thom!
噢， 抱歉， 不好意思
Ohp- Sorry! Sorry.
聽著， 希莉亞
Look Celia.
我們必須順著我們的感覺走
We have to follow our passions.
你熱愛機械工學...
You have your robotics...
... 而我只是想去太空中耍帥一下
...and I just want to be awesome in space.
好的， 它們來了。 還有兩分鐘！
Okay, they're coming. Two minutes left!
快點， 湯姆！
Speed it up, Thom!
生動一點！
Vivacissimo!
你為什麼不肯承認被我的機械手臂嚇壞了？
Why don't you just admit that you're freaked out by my robot hand?
聽著， 希莉亞， 我那時還年輕...
Listen Celia, I was young...
... 只是個小屁孩
...and a dick.
但是這不是毀滅這個世界的理由
But that's no reason to destroy the world.
他為啥要這麼說？
Why does he do this?
我們已經試過這個情景了！
We already tried that one!
中止！
Abort!
停！
Cut!
噢啊啊啊！
Whoaaa!
不...
Nooooo!
你傷透了我的心
You broke my heart.
我知道
I know.
你把我拋棄在地球上
You forgot me on earth.
我知道
I know.
我應該把你碎屍萬段
I should just crush you.
對...
I'm-
對不起
I'm sorry.
說的很自然
Good ad-lib.
這不是我的錯！
Not my fault!
這次
This time.
上面安靜點！
Quiet on set!
我們沒時間了！
We're out of time!
快點！
Come on!
啊...
RAAAAAAAAH!
記憶覆寫， 90%
Memory overwrite, 90%.
隊長！ 我們必須放棄了！
Captain! We have to abort!
這個世界已經不一樣了， 希莉亞...
The world's changed, Celia...
... 或許， 我們也可以改變
...maybe we can too.
記憶覆寫完成！
Memory overwrite complete!
你知道嗎
You know.
我們可以從中學到一課
There's a lesson to be learned from this.
也是有可能更糟的
Could'a gone worse.